modaco.com 2012-06-01

# MoDaCo - Privacy Policy - Website - MoDaCo

###  [ #1 ](http://www.modaco.com/topic/239953-modaco-privacy-policy/#entry733839 "MoDaCo - Privacy Policy: post #1")

Posted 23 April 2006 - 10:27 PM

PaulOBrien

  * Gender:Male
  * Location:Norwich, UK
  * Devices:One X / TF Prime
  * Twitter:[@paulobrien](http://twitter.com/paulobrien)

**Privacy Statement**

_1\. Visitor Notice_

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are asked to register before participating on the forums, entering a contest, or ordering e-mail newsletters. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.  

  * To help you quickly find services or information on MoDaCo.  

  * To help us create content most relevant to you.  

  * To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services from MoDaCo.

_2\. Visitor Consent_

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the features on MoDaCo, but you will not be able to access areas that require registration. MoDaCo may offer newsletters, which are sent only to opt-in lists. They also include a very easy and simple way to be removed once you have joined.

_3\. Financial Information_

MoDaCo does not retain any of your financial information used to make purchases in the MoDaCo store.

_4\. Security_

MoDaCo strictly protects the security of your personal information and honours your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorised access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

_5\. Distribution of personal information_

MoDaCo does not distribute personal information to any third parties. Should this change, MoDaCo will not distribute any information without your prior express consent. Please be aware that it may be possible, depending on your use of various features on MoDaCo, that some of your personal information is available on publicly accessible web page(s). One example would be using the MoDaCo forums. Consent to expose some of your personal information in these cases is implied by the use of these features.

_6\. Hosted Sites_

MoDaCo gives children between the ages of 13 and 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to public forums and message boards. As always, exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in a public forum. In order to comply with the COPPA ruling, if you are younger than 13 years of age, you are forbidden from becoming a member of MoDaCo or posting information on MoDaCo message boards without direct parental consent.

_7\. Enforcement_

If for some reason you believe MoDaCo has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail using the details below and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Please ensure the words 'Privacy Policy' are in the Subject line.

_8\. Changes to this document_

Changes to this document may be made any time without warning. MoDaCo may or may not notify you of changes in this policy, however, we will make an effort to notify you if there are any major changes to this policy. You will not be notified about changes related to clarification and/or elaboration of parts of this policy.

_Notice to Parents_

Parents or guardians: we want to help you guard your children's privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.

###  [ #2 ](http://www.modaco.com/topic/239953-modaco-privacy-policy/#entry1759491 "MoDaCo - Privacy Policy: post #2")

PaulOBrien 

Posted 14 July 2011 - 12:28 PM

PaulOBrien

  * Gender:Male
  * Location:Norwich, UK
  * Devices:One X / TF Prime
  * Twitter:[@paulobrien](http://twitter.com/paulobrien)

**Contact Details**

_These details are for use only in relation to purchases from the MoDaCo store!_

If you have a query regarding your MoDaCo purchase, they should be directed in the first instance for Forum@MoDaCo.com by email.

Our company is based in Diss, Norfolk, United Kingdom. Our Customer Service number (for Store purchase related queries only) is 01379 888 101.

  *[23 April 2006 - 10:27 PM]: 2006-04-23T22:27:31+00:00
  *[14 July 2011 - 12:28 PM]: 2011-07-14T12:28:33+00:00
